dimonsterus
димонстерус
otre paragraph AB of part two of article 158 of the
отре пунктом АБ части второй статьи 158
UKRF under the following circumstances,
УКРФ при следующих обстоятельствах
let's talk normally
давайте нормально пообщаемся
My name is Andrey you are
Меня зовут Андрей вы вас
your name is Anastasia Nastya And your
как меня зовут Анастасия Настя А вашего
colleague colleague
коллегу коллегу
Dima dimonsterus
Дима димонстерус
and what are we talking about
а чём мы с тобой общаемся о
life is hard hard your life is
жизни тяжело тяжёлая у тебя жизнь
dimon-16
димон-16
dimonsterus
димонстерус
Diman carefully  answer battle I can after
Диман аккуратно отвечай боя могу после
this
этого
this And how much Nastya How much is real You are
это А сколько Настя Сколько реально Вы
not together I love it so much when I meet
вместе не Я так люблю когда встречаю
people who really love each
людей которые действительно любят друг
other This is very wonderful in modern times
друга Это очень прекрасно в современном
this is a very rare thing in the world We
мире это очень редкость большая Мы очень
love each other very much
любим друг друга
Dimo ​​And tell me, do you love Nastya Nastya Well,
Димо А скажите вы любите Настю Настю Ну
of course, why do you love
а как во конечно А за что вы любите
Nastya? You love Nastya for this
Настю любите Настя вот за вот такую вот
pig that eats on camera
свинью которая на камеру
and what city are you from Barnau couple
ест а из какого вы города парочка барнау
What are you talking about me  in YouTu filming is not just
Ты меня что в YouTu снима не просто
interesting ban it’s
интересно бану это
Altai Alta my dad served in the
Алтай Алта у меня батя служил в
Altai region somewhere near
Алтайском крае где-то под
Barnaul Russian I’m from Rostov myself
барнаулом русский Я из Ростова сам родом
but now I live in California 18  in
но сейчас в Калифорнии живу 18 лет через
2 years you will be
2 года будет
twenty, don’t swear, but that’s not the
двадцатом не ругаешься Да не это ж
Ukrainians, let them swear, let them
украинцы они пусть ругаются пусть
swear. Well, here I am playing with the
ругаются Ну вот а я тут играю с
Ukrainians with the
украинска с
Ukrainians at the table, what do you play, what do
украинцами шка за столом в что играешь
you play, meet like this, the Ukrainians eat
играешь встречай вот так украинцы жру
flour And they say to me, ugh Come here and
мку А они мне говорят фу Иди сюда и
they start yelling at me and you know
начинают орать на меня а меня это знаешь
how it turns me on Yes, I want more
как заводит заводит Да щ больше хочется
Cham Kat to
Чам Кать
them you basically
им ты в принципе после этого
get excited after that and Dimona  then
возбуждаешься и Димона а потом
Yes, well, everyone has
Да ну У каждого есть
their own fetish Okay, let's go, Ukrainians,
свой фетиш Ладно мы пойдём украинцы не
don't let's talk normally, let's
давай поговорим нормально давам
eat normally, I need to finish the Ukrainians, so
нормально доедай мне надо украинцев так
I'm from Ukraine, Glory to
я из Украины Слава
Ukraine,
Украине
you, I'm in Khmelnitsy, naty, you, Glory to
ты Я в хмельниц наты вы Слава
got it, you're rubbing booze or something. Come on, let's eat
поняла ты потирать бу что ли Давай давай
and let's go and turn it on  turned on you
жри и давай о пошла включили включили ты
come on come on come on come on let
давай давай давай
me Post it on
давай давай меня Выложи в
Tik you want
Tik ты хочешь чтобы
people I want to be popular to be popular
люди Я хочу популярной быть популярной
then I don’t want to yet  just Like if it’s
тогда пока не хочется просто Типа если
popular
популяр
Come on Dean I sympathize with you Even though you’re a
давай Дин я тея сочувствую Ты хоть и
dude from
чувак из
Russia, damn it, I now understand that guys
России блин я теперь понимаю что пацаны
go to war to die Because
короче на войну идут умереть Потому что
life is like that, it’s hard,
жизнь такая это тяжело
tell me already in
скажи уже во
a year that you’re not this until now
года что ты не это до сих пор До сих пор
I’m yours  It’s not like you could have tied a grenade to her,
я вашей не так можно же было ей гранату
in short, a U-turn would have been possible. Yes, yours
короче разворот бы её Да ваши ваши
understand. Prim, they tied you to two
понимаешь Прим тебе к двум
in Russian, even the Russian doesn’t know.
по-русски даже русский не знает Вот ты
You’re not Russian. You’re not Russian, but you’re Russian.
не русская Ты не русская а ты русский-то
You’re not Russian.  you're not Russian you
Ты не русская не русская ты по-русски
speak Russian and you're not Russian
говори а ты не русская
Come on let's
Давай давай
run go The way you look at Zelensky it
бегом иди Как смотрит ты на Зеленского
looks like you and him are probably brothers damn it's
похоже вообще вы с ним наверно братья
not scary to be like Zelensky it's scary to be like like it's
блин на Зеленского не страшно быть
not scary to be like Zelensky it's like to
похожим не страшно на Зеленского похоже
be like Nastya Nastya is Zelensky
быть похожим Настя Настя так Зеленский
this is
же в это
Nastya
Настя
Zelensky, Nastya’s face is so open, it’s just
Зеленский у Насти так открывается просто
tough how you sleep with her, her
жесть как ты с ней спишь У неё же
face is in front of her. Do you hear me say,
противо лицо лицо Слышишь я говорю ты
take this off?  wait for a rag on this
сними эту тряпку подожди ты во на эту
Nastya in general or not or not Which Nastya
Настю вообще или нет или нет Какой Настю
he says Nastya name is which Nastya
он говорит Настя зовут какой Настя
says I don’t remember at all You said
говорит я вообще не пому Ты же сказала
Nastya he’s a
Настя он
dimonsterus I eat all the time Are you
димонстерус я постоянно ем Ты что
hungry Nastyukha She stupidly
Настюха проголодалась Она тупо
now means vyser vyser everyday
сейчас значит высер высер
life to feed
быт напитать
I wait now burp  will come
я жди сейчас отрыжка придёт
soon so Alexey you are 29 years old and you
скоро так Алексей вып тебе 29 лет и ты
live with this one we
живёшь С этой
don’t know
не знаем
that you were on the fourth day
такого тебе четвёртого числа был от день
niya 29 years old 29 years old who has you and you and you
ния 29 лет 29 лет у кого ты и ты и ты
really want to live with
реально хочешь до 30 лет жить с
this young twenty-nine-year-old Lyokha
этой молодой двадцати девятилетний Лёха
Lyokha ha until you're 30 What Lyokha, what are you not she's
Лёха ха Какой Лёха то ты что не не это
you Alexey
она ты Алексей
I'm actually not
я вообще-то не
Alexey I'm
Алексей
scared it's
испугалась это
you
ты
come on
давай
No you're
Нет вы
the ones  what are you
те что ша вы
with you, that we don’t know any Alyosha,
у тебя чт мы не знаем никаких Алёша
what are
вы какие л
you, November 4, date of
ты 4 ноября дено п года
birth,
рождения
so now let’s see what you were brought in for,
так сейчас посмотрим за что привлекался
nothing to do, someone is looking, then in
нечем кого-то смотрит то
general,
вообще
now we are you  we'll find you now
так сейчас мы тебя найдём сейчас мы тебя
we'll find you don't run away now
твоя всё про тебя
I'll find out everything about you I know everything she knows everything about me
узнаю Я всё знаю она всё про меня знает
if you want to know
если ты хочешь знать
like this
так
So where did she
Так куда
run away she took a screenshot from Shotik with a
убежала она сделала скриншотит с Шотик с
fright
перепугу
who
кого
now I'm punching now now Lyokha already
сейчас я сейчас пробиваю сейчас Лёха уже
pierced
пробитый
Lyokha already
Лёха уже
pierced like
пробитый так
that  Yeah
так Угу
Yeah Yes Marik Thank you Yes Marik
Угу Да Марик Спасибо Да Марик
Thank you so ancestors Alexey vykh Alexey
Спасибо так предки Алексей вых Алексей
Krasnoshchekovsky District Court of the Altai
краснощёковский районный суд Алтайского
Territory of the Altai Territory  so the prosecutor
края Алтайского края так прокурор
Emelyanova Olga Yuryevna Yuryevna
Емельянова Ольга Юрьевна Юрьевна
corrections Evgeniy Vladimirovich corrections
выправки Евгений Владимирович выправки
Alexey Vladimi Let's see now
Алексей владими Посмотрим сейчас
let's see like
посмотрим так
this the Krasnoshchekovsky district court of the
так краснощёковский районный суд ный суд
Altai Territory arrived
Алтайского края поступило
Yes you Pritski Alexey Vladimirovich
Да вы Прицки Алексей Владимирович
Alexey
Алексей
Vladimirovich the
Владимирович приговор
verdict the verdict in the name of the Russian Federation and the
приговор именем Российской Федерации и
Russian Federation so with the participation
Российской Федерации так с участием
of the state prosecutor pony
государстве обвинителя пони
prosecution of the defendants hellish
проку подсудимых вых адских
ev defense lawyer
ев защитников адвоката
so so
так так
dawat so that he
давата так что он
committed the crime
сдела совершил преступление
provided for in paragraph a of part two of
предусмотрено пунктом а части второй
Article 158 of the Criminal Code under the following
статьи 158 УКРФ при следующих
circumstances under the following
обстоятельствах при следующих
circumstances the period of time from 23:00 on
обстоятельства период времени с 23:00
05/29/22 to 1315 on 30/05 2 More precise
29.05.22 до 1315 30.05 2 Более точные
data and time have not been established by the investigation as to whether
данные и время следствием не установлены
you are producing an AB located at
вы продки АВ находящегося по месту
your place of residence  at the address So
своего проживания по адресу Так
knowing for certain that in the
достоверно знающей что в помещение
garage at the address there is a
гаража по адресу находится автомобиль
VAZ
ВАЗ
21061 car with a state registration
21061 с государственным регистрационным
plate number on which
знаком номер на котором установлена
a battery belonging to x was installed
аккумуляторная батарея принадлежащая х
where he had a criminal intent
где у него возник Преступный умысел
aimed at secretly stealing
направленный на тайное хищение
a battery and
аккумуляторной батареи и другого
any other valuable property
какого-либо ценного имущества
belonging to x from the garage premises at the
принадлежащего х из помещения гаража по
address by a group of persons in a preliminary
адресу группой лиц по предварительному
conspiracy with illegal entry into
сговору с незаконным проникновением в
another storage facility, after which theft of the battery for
иное хранилище после чего вып ких ав с
the purpose of sale  conceived in his
целью реализации задуманного в своём
criminal intent for the above period of
преступном умысле вышеуказанный период
time, being at the above
времени находясь по вышеуказанному
address, he informed Vypskikh and offered to
адресу сообщил вып ских ев и предложил
carry out
совершить повсеместно Да и совершить
secret things with him everywhere and everywhere  so
повсеместно с ним тайные так так так
one
одну
second
секунду
op so now
оп так сейчас
connected so Criminal conspiracy to
подключили так Преступный сговор на
secretly rechargeable batteries and
тайно аккумуляторные батареи и другого
other valuable property at the
какого-либо ценно имущество пожа
premises at the address group list after
помещени жа по адресу группа лист после
which the issuance of AB and issuance in the period from
чего выд АВ и выд ев в период времени с
23:00 so so so More
23:00 так так так Более
accurate
точные
so distributed between  constitute criminal
так распределили между собой преступные
roles, according to which the officer had to
роли Согласно которых вып ев должен был
monitor the situation and, in the event of
наблюдать за обстановкой и в случае
unauthorized persons appearing, warn the
появления посторонних лиц предупредить
officer about this so that they could
об этом вып АВ для того чтобы они могли
escape from the scene of the crime
скрыться с места совершения преступления
that is, his brother stood on the nix
то есть братюня у него стоял на шухере
so you are the ancestors of AB so that this Alekha
так вы предки АВ тобто вот этот Алёха
was supposed to penetrate into the garage in order to
должен был проникнуть в гараж с целью
detect the theft of a
обнаружения хищения аккумуляторной
battery and any other
батареи и другого какого-либо
property, realizing his joint
имущества реализуя свой совместный
Criminal intent, direct And why are you not
Преступный умысел направи А что ты не
so fun already? Come on  I wanted to become
так весело уже А давай ты ж хотела стать
famous now you will become famous
знаменитой сейчас станете знаменитыми
So realistic how much is written there Let’s say
Так реали сколько там написано Давай
in short what they
короче что ему
awarded him and this is them they are still there wait
присудили а это они они ещё там подожди
so they disappeared in short So as a result of
так скрылись короче Так в результате
joint  criminal actions of the ex-vics
совместных преступных действий вып вых
caused material damage for a total
причинили материальный Ущерб на общую
amount of
сумму
rubles per 50
руб на 50
bucks which is less than 50
бак который меньше 50
bucks so let’s see that he was beaten
баксов так Смотрим что ему лупили
so qualified so at the court
так квалифицированы так в судебном
hearing the defendants of the ex-vics clarified
заседании подсудимые вых вых прояснили
that they understand that when charged they agree with him
что им понятно при обвинение они с ним
admit their guilt in
согласны признают свою вину в полном
full Oh  so supports the petition of the deputy
объёме Ой так поддерживает ходатайство
during the investigation blah blah blah so the court
зам ходе следствия бла-бла-бла так суд
established the
установил там
text there So a crime of average
текста Так преступление средней
gravity place of residence by the head of
тяжести месту жительства главой
the administration  Suetsky village council, otherwise
администрации суетского сельсовета а то
you still live in everyone and not in Barnaul,
вы ещ в сех живёте а не в Барнауле
Krasnoshchekovsky district of the Altai Territory,
краснощековского района Алтайского края
you are in Sovetskoe rural Vet Ponya are
вы в Советском сельско Вете Поня
registered as characterized
прописаны так характеризуется
satisfactorily as circumstances,
удовлетворительно так обстоятельствами
mitigating punishment in accordance with
смягчающее наказание в соответствии со
Article 61 of the Criminal Code, the court recognizes the
статьёй 61 УК суд признаёт полное
defendant’s full confession of guilt, remorse
признание подсудимого сво вины раскаяние
for what he did blah blah  -blah
в содеянном бла-бла-бла
so oh so so so
так ой
awarded let's do it
так так так что присудили давай мы
now  let's skip here read 2 years
сейчас пропустим тут читать 2 года
sentenced to find this bro
приговорил признать вып ев это братана
guilty of committing a crime
его виновным в совершении преступления
provided for in paragraph
предусмотренного пунктом
AB part two 158 and assign him
АБ часть вторая 158 и назначим ему
a sentence of imprisonment for a period of
наказание в виде лишения свободы сроком
1 year and 6 months on the
на 1 год и 6 месяцев на
basis of the assigned instructions in the form of
основании назначено указания в виде
imprisonment to be considered a suspended solo
лишения свободы считать условным сольным
term for  2 years so the bro received
сроком на 2 года так братюня получил
a condition so out so recognize the bearings of AV
условку так вых так признать выправки АВ
that is, this Lyokha is guilty of committing a
то есть этого Лёху виновным в совершении
crime stipulated
преступления предусмотренного
so-so-so we will assign a punishment of  in the form of
так-так-так назначим наказание в виде
imprisonment for a period of 2 years 6
лишения свободы сроком на 2 года 6
months on the basis of Article 73 of the Criminal Code of the Russian Federation,
месяцев на основании статьи 73 УКРФ
the punishment imposed for punishment in the form of
назначенное за наказание наказание виде
imprisonment is considered suspended with a
лишения свободы считать условным с
probationary period of 2 years and the entire
испытательным сроком на 2 года так и всё
probationary period is calculated from the moment
испытательный срок исчисляется с момента
the sentence enters into legal force
вступления приговора в законную силу
blah blah blah then you are shorter
бла-бла-бла то ты короче
this is to go battery for
такое пойти аккумулятор за
50 less than 5,000 rubles together topic got caught
50 меньше 5.000 руб вдвоём тема попались
got caught so is
попались так
there anything else
а есть ещё
interesting for the Twentieth year dy
интересно за Двадцатый год дй
year so  Krasnoshchekovsky District Court of the
год так краснощёковский районный суд
Poltava Territory, consisting of the press
Полтавского края в составе так прес
secretary Savina of the administrative Ministry of Internal Affairs of
секретаре савины административной МВД
Russia So what
России Так а что ты там
did you do there? And in short, the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Russia went
сделал А по короче МВД России обратилась
to
в
court to establish additional
суд об установлении дополнительных
administrative restrictions to change the
административных ограничений изменения
established administrative
установленного административного
restriction regarding the carriage of aircraft in the
ограничения в отношении выправки АВ в
form of a ban on staying in
виде запрета пребывания в местах
public catering places so that  he didn’t go
общественного питания чтобы он не ходил
to nalivayki So where is the
в наливайки Так где осуществляется
sale and drinking of alcoholic beverages carried out and
продажа и распитие спиртных напитков и
the obligation to appear three times a month
обязанности появляться три раза в месяц
at the internal affairs agency at your place of
в орган внутренних дел по месту
residence, you were forbidden to eat  Those through the
жительства есть тебе запретили те через
court were banned from appearing in bars
суд запретили появляться в барах
and came once every 3 months.
и раз в 3 месяца приходили
Come on, in support of
Давай в обосновании предъявленные
the demands presented, he indicated that so
требования указал что так
27022 Rubtsovsky City Court of the
27022 рубцовским городским судом
Altai Territory in relation to this attack
Алтайского края в отношении этого выпад
they established administrative supervision for a
их установлено административный надзор
period of 3 years;
сроком на 3 года ему установлены
restrictions were established in the form of a ban on staying in
ограничения в виде запрета пребывания в
non-residential or other  premises that are a
нежилого или иного помещения являющееся
place of residence or stay from 22
местом жительства либо пребывания с 22
yes, that is, you are not allowed to go out at
да то есть тебе нельзя выходить короче
night from
ночью с
10 pm to 6:00 am So the obligation to
10 вечера 6:00 утра Так обязанности
appear twice a month for VVD  at the place
являться два раза в месяц ВВД по месту
of residence or stay Yes, uh, a ban on
жительства или пребывания Да ээ запрета
traveling outside the territory of the Krasnoshchekovsky
выезжать за территорию краснощёковского
district, a ban on staying in preschool
района запрет о пребывания в дошкольных
and secondary educational institutions,
и средних образовательных учреждениях
it is forbidden for someone like you to approach
нельзя такому как тебе подходить к
kindergartens and schools, and in institutions and
садикам и школам так в учреждениях
organizations involved in organizing
организациях участвующих в организации
recreation, health care
отдыха оздоровления медицинского
provision for
обеспечения
minors, including those
несовершеннолетний и в том числе
intended for
предназначенных для проведения
mass cultural and interesting Why is
культурно-массовых та интересно А почему
this so during the stay? So you
так во время нахождения Так вы приск
committed violation of established
допускал нарушение установленных
restrictions and also committed an
ограничения также совершал
administrative offense against the
административные правонарушение против
rule of law, namely
правопорядка управления а именно
07/18/20 to commit an administrative
18.07.20 совершить административное
offense is provided for by part of the
правонарушение предусмотрено часть пер
1924 cop of the Russian Federation
1924 коп РФ
07/28/20 to commit an administrative
28.07.20 соверши административное
offense is provided for and there are also
правонарушение предусмотрено так ещё там
five or six of these offenses
пять или шесть правонарушений этих
listed at the court hearing by a
перечисляется в судебном заседании
representative of the administrative office.
представителя административного ица
there’s more to read and
стала Так там это там ещё читать и
read,
читать
not this awesome video, this is Yes, Marik
не это обалденный ролик это Да Марик его
slapped him in the face And I also  struck
по лицу снол А я ещ пробил
there is a court decision Yes, enter his
есть судебное решение Да вводишь его
last name name In short, everything is the Altai Territory, he is
фамилию имя Короче всё Алтайский край он
definitely that’s all,
однозначно вот и всё
yes the format could be written to th Telegram
да формат може бы пись на й Telegram
directly at once axis VN
прям зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube borrowing
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg Orcs in your ban and even more
нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и дуже
richly video not  I show people sometimes I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about the stream Tom for this
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
purpose, Mali is operational  link to
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
be written directly at once and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegra okrim video schezh tsikava and
телегра окрим видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and we are guilty of you trimati
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
write L
пиши L